♪ Here we are going far ♪
♪ to save all that we love ♪
♪ If we give all we’ve got ♪
♪ we will make it through ♪
♪ Here we are like a star ♪
♪ shining bright
on your world today ♪
♪ Make evil go away ♪
♪ Code Lyoko we’ll
withstand it all ♪
♪ Code Lyoko be there
when you call ♪
♪ Code Lyoko we
will stand real tall ♪
♪ Code Lyoko
stronger after all ♪
Hey, Aelita?
Are you connected?
Hello, Jeremie.
Did you have a good day?
Uh, nothing special.
Which classes do you have
tomorrow morning?
First, we’ve got physics,
and chemistry with Miss Hertz,
and then a math exam
with Misses Meyer.
What do you do during an exam?
You have to show
what you know in writing.
What a strange idea.
Not really,
because we’re not like you.
Your memory and ours
aren’t the same
because yours is, well, infinite.
Our brains have a
limited memory capacity.
We can’t store as much
data as you can.
In other words, Aelita,
compared to you, our hard disk
comes up kind of short.
Oh, I get it.
Are you sleeping yet!?
I’m gonna be in trouble
if I stay connected.
I’m sorry, Aelita, but…
I gotta go.
I don’t want to take the chance of
having to introduce you to Jim.
I’ll connect with you
at noon tomorrow
universal time.
(RINGS)
(MUSIC)
(SCHOOL BELL RINGS)
Something wrong, Jeremie?
A problem?
No, no. I finished, mam.
Why, yes you have.
Very good job.
It’s excellent work, too.
Alright, the rest of you
keep working.
Oh! Her birthday is today!
You may go, Jeremie.
Thanks a million! You could’ve
at least stayed and given me a hand!
Aelita. I almost forgot that we met
exactly a year ago today.
Hey, it’s Aelita’s birthday today.
Yeah, I forgot all about it.
What’s going on?
Mind your own business.
Wow, it’s already a year
since we met Aelita.
And I still haven’t
managed to materialize her.
I know, but we’ve managed
to protect her from XANA.
What do you say we use our lunch hour
to prepare a little surprise?
She’d like that a lot, huh,
don’t you think?
Good idea.
What do you think, Jeremie?
Yeah, come on!
Let’s go to the factory!
You go on ahead.
I promised Yumi
I’d stop by after class.
We’ll meet you there.
Oh, I thought they
would never leave.
You friends really
stick to you like glue, huh?
Not half as much as you do, Sissi.
I’d like to talk to you, Ulrich.
Could we have lunch together?
I mean, just us two?
Uh, sorry.
Yumi’s waiting for me.
Yumi! Always Yumi!
It’s time he dumped her!
(PULSING)
(SINISTER MUSIC)
Yeah!
I’d love to find
a nice present for Aelita.
No problem!
Why don’t you program
a digital birthday cake!
Very funny.
What’s wrong, Einstein?
Power cut, I guess.
Come on, we’ll go check the
fuses in the control room.
What do you think?
It’s a great idea…
I really wonder
what he sees in her.
Okay, let’s go.
Coast is clear.
Wow.
I forgot what this place looked like!
That’s really cool.
You’re kidding.
A hunk of junk if you ask me.
I’m gonna beat you the the elevator!
We’ll see!
Yee-ha-haw!
I won!
That’s nice.
They sent it back down.
Odd must be
in the scanner already.
Well, well.
Nice little hiding place.
What are you doing here?
I should ask you that!
I want to know…
are Jeremie and Odd waiting for you,
or is this your own private love nest?
Sissi, that is none of your business.
Yumi’s right.
So why don’t you just leave?
Huh? What’s going on?
Something’s wrong.
It doesn’t want to open.
It won’t start up.
But what’s the matter?
I don’t know. It’s blocked.
Aaaaaah!
(CRASHING)
What was that?
Better check it out.
It’s a trap!
XANA.
Ulrich?
Ulrich, are you okay?
Answer me!
I can’t seem to move my arm.
And you?
I was lucky. I’m okay.
But not her. She’s out cold.
I better call Jeremie.
(CELL PHONE RINGS)
Yumi, are you alright?
In that elevator?
So that was the noise we heard.
We’re stuck in the machine room.
Careful!
It looks as if we’re on our own, Ulrich.
You’ve gotta go back up.
You have to get to the lab.
And what about you?
With just one arm?
Impossible.
Besides, we can’t leave Sissi all alone.
Odd!
H-a-a-a-a-h!
Jeremie.
Jeremie, please answer me.
Where are you?
Whoa.
What’s the problem?
I, uh…
just remembered I have
a slight fear of heights
Just hang on tight,
and don’t look down.
You can do it, Yumi.
What happened? I can’t…
The elevator broke down.
We’re stuck down in the shaft.
Oh, I’m so cold.
Don’t worry, we’ll be
outta here real soon.
(WINCES)
Ulrich, what is it?
I think I broke my arm.
Let me have a look at it.
We’ve gotta get out of here
No kidding, genius!
Aah!
Jeremie!
Aaah!
Let me go, you horrible--!
Up here! Hurry!
Follow me!
It’s too bad this isn’t Lyoko.
At least I have superpowers there.
I’m pretty sure Aelita is also in danger.
And she’s gonna need your help.
But how do we reach the lab?
Via the boiler room.
(CELL PHONE RINGS)
Hello, Odd. Are you alright?
Where are you?
Heading for the lab.
And how are you doing?
Let’s say I’m trying to cope.
Aaah!
Oh, look at the boiler.
XANA’s really after us this time.
Yumi’s on her way to the lab.
She’s climbing up the shaft.
(HISSING)
Huh?
I don’t trust that thing.
Ready for a hundred-yard dash?
I’m better at math than gym.
Math isn’t gonna help you this time.
Ready?
Go!
Yeah!
Hey! What’s that noise?
Uh, nothing.
Don’t move, wait.
There. Okay.
Thank you.
You know, you’re a real good nurse.
Ah.
I’m not just somebody
who sticks to you like glue, huh?
Hm?
(CELESTIAL HUMMING)
♪ Ah… ♪
Bye-bye!
Odd? Jeremie?
Odd! Jeremie! Please answer!
(COUGHING)
You’re here!
I was so scared!
(LAUGHS)
We pushed the boiler too hard.
Guess it just couldn’t take it.
Oh, I don’t believe it!
This is useless!
Lyoko connection.
Please wait.
This is absolutely Impossible!
Here we go.
I’ve launched a scan
to find the exact position
of the activated tower.
Aelita!
Aelita? Do you read me, Aelita?
Oh. I understand, Ulrich.
How is Sissi?
She’s okay.
Hang on. We’re off to Lyoko.
Okay, good luck.
The water is rising,
and Ulrich can’t swim
with a broken arm.
And I can’t contact Aelita.
Okay, I’ve got the coordinates of the tower.
Now, I’ve got to--
Jeremie!
Aelita! How are you?
Everything okay?
I’ve been trying to
contact you for such a long time.
We had a problem.
XANA set a trap for us
in the factory.
Ulrich is in danger.
Yumi and Odd are coming to Lyoko.
We’ve gotta hurry.
I’m just in front of the tower.
And to think I dreamed of
being alone with you
for such a long time,
but this isn’t
what I had in mind at all!
I swear, if we get out of here alive,
I’ll be nicer to you in the future, Sissi.
Really?
Jeremie and the others
are gonna call for help, aren’t they?
Yeah, I guess you could call it that.
They had better hurry up!
Otherwise, we’ll drown before you
have a chance to be nicer to me!
Okay.
Yumi and Odd, we’re ready to go.
You’re off to the desert.
Transfer Yumi.
Transfer Odd.
Jeremie!
Hold on, Ulrich.
Odd and Yumi are gonna be transferred.
Hang on for just a second.
Hurry, Jeremie.
It’s getting tough.
We can hardly
touch bottom anymore.
Okay, now.
Back to the virtualization.
Scanner Odd.
Scanner Yumi.
Virtualization!
You missed!
Okay, Aelita.
It’s time. You ready?
Okay, guys! We’ll force our way through!
You keep running behind us.
We’ve got to make it
to the tower, you understand!
Go!
Take that!
And that!
40 life points
in just two shots!
Odd, you’re losing life points
much too quickly!
Don’t worry, I’ll make it!
Watch out on your left!
Laser arrow!
Huh?
Your point loss rate
is too high, Odd, you hear!
Agh!
Whoa--aah!
Oh, no! Aelita!
Aelita, 80!
Yumi, just 10!
You’ve gotta clear the passage!
Hiyah!
Aah!
No!
It’s okay, Ulrich.
Aelita’s in the tower!
Ulrich?
Ulrich, do you hear me?
Return to the past now.
Okay, now!
Ready, Aelita?
Mhmm!
Here we go!
What’s going on?
I don’t understand.
It’s something from our world.
Shh!
Happy birthday, Aelita!
Oh!
I don’t get it.
We’re celebrating because it’s exactly
one year ago that we met you.
Oh, I see.
And am I supposed
to do something?
Yeah, save me a piece of cake!
One-track mind.
Don’t listen to that glutton!
Speak for yourself, four-eyes!
Calm down, you guys!
Hah! What a bunch of loonies.
They’re celebrating
their computer’s birthday!
Well, I think it’s a
very trendy thing to do.
Buy a cake for tomorrow.
To celebrate the birthday
of my makeup kit.
Odd, you’re eating all the cake! Stop!
I’m hungry!
So is everybody else!
Hand it over.
CLOSED CAPTIONING PROVIDED BY
REDDIT.COM/R/CODELYOKO